Everyone, me Kevin here. Boy oh boy, I
am going to break down nine stocks in
this video. And I have to say a lot of
people have been asking me, Kevin, what
do you think about Tom Lee saying 2027
is going to be one heck of a rally? And
I have two things to say about that.
One, the guy always thinks there's going
to be a rally. Two, he's not bullish
enough for 2026. See, I actually think
that, and we mentioned this in our
SpaceX analysis videos before SpaceX
went public, I actually think Elon Musk
is going to spend every dime that he
raises like a drunken sailor on
hardware. [laughter]
And literally last week, their earnings
call told us and their financials told
us that 85 cents out of every dollar of
capex is going right into AI hardware.
So in this video, we are going to break
down which stocks could be great AI
hardware opportunities. uh given that we
expect Elon will drunk like spend like
crazy on macro and mini hard plus the
coming Terrafab which there are stocks
in here that relate directly to Terapab
as well. I just want to be really clear
because sometimes people who only read
titles or just don't actually watch the
video don't get it. So maybe if I put it
at the beginning of the video I could
get over this. We have over 7 figures of
exposure to SpaceX in our venture
capital fund. We bought this puppy at
like $330 uh billion. Obviously, that
means we're up like 5x. Okay, great.
We'll see when we actually get the
shares. We don't hold the shares yet.
Even though some lockups have started,
we have no idea when the shares are
actually going to show up for us. when I
make videos that outline when I would be
willing to buy more of SpaceX stock sub
$80. That doesn't mean I think it's
going to $80. It means I don't want to
buy it unless it's sub $80. I wouldn't
add more like our original position. But
this video isn't about investing in
SpaceX. It's not to be bearish on
SpaceX. It's not to be bullish on
SpaceX. The only thing this video does
is say if we believe that Elon is going
to spend like a drunken sailor,
where are the beneficiaries gonna be?
[laughter]
Okay, now that I got that out of the
way, let's get started and we'll cover
these nine stocks. Keep in mind, this
does not include memory on purpose.
Memory is going to be a totally
different video. We might even do some
of these stocks as a deep dive. You
could leave a comment, ask me if you
want any kind of deep dives, but we're
just going to focus on nine different
stocks outside of memory. So, first rack
count. Base case. Current Foxcon order
for Macro Mini Hard 13,000 racks. That's
about 52.5ish billion dollars of spend.
That order is already in. The fact that
that order is going to Fox Con is really
going to impact one of the stocks on
this uh nine sheet list.
There is also this opium circulating
right now because of this semianalysis
piece that everybody on X is talking
about. I when the article dropped left a
comment within minutes of their post and
I'm like, "Hey, you guys you guys have
an error in your piece. Nobody gives a
fly in Hoodie duty." But the semi
analysis bull case is that we're not
actually going to see 13,000 racks
ordered for macro mini hard. That's the
current projection. The current
projection from semi analysis on a bull
case is that we'll actually see 68,800
rack orders. So 68800 divided by 13,000
is basically 5.3x the orders, which
works out to somewhere like $275 billion
of spent, maybe even as much as $320
billion of spent. And this is where
people say, okay, well, like what's this
predicated on? Is this predicated on net
income projections? Well, that's the
issue I have with the semi analysis
piece. You know, my my argument is how
can you argue Elon's going to earn $15
to $20 per GPU hour and then in the same
damn article say Anthropic's only going
to pay $3 per GPU hour. Like, you can't
you can't bias to the most bullish
direction in both ways by giving it as a
discount to the LLMs and a premium to
Elon. That doesn't work because the LLMs
are paying Elon, right? [laughter] Like
if you're going to use 15 per GPU hour,
use it to both. Of course, nobody's
replied. So, whatever. But people on X
or people who just do little GPT
summaries of stuff, they don't care cuz
they don't have the patience to
understand nuance. And that's okay cuz
it creates opportunities for people like
you and me. [laughter] So,
my opinion though is that it doesn't
really matter because Elon doesn't
really care. This is between you and me,
okay? Doesn't really care about the
earnings. I know, I know that sounds
crazy to say, but I think Elon will
literally expand supply no matter what
because he's drunk on the idea of, "Oh
my god, we need so many data centers.
Like, we need to get to space and then
we're going to have like millions of
chips that we're going to have to make
for all the Optimus robots. Oh my gosh."
Mind you, we're like a decade away,
right? On day after Christmas, doesn't
matter. Doesn't matter whether FSD
happens or orbital satellites happen.
Doesn't matter. None of that freaking
crap matters. All that matters is that
the richest guy in the world believes
it. And if the richest guy in the world
believes it, he's going to blow a lot of
money whether he gets an ROI or not. And
there are some big stocks that are going
to benefit from this upfront. The first
one on the list is Nvidia.
It doesn't matter if Elon makes an ROI,
they are going to go
[laughter]
every single time an Elon order comes
in. It's no surprise that Jensen cozies
up to Elon and calls him, you know, the
greatest ever whatever, right? The goat.
It's because he's a big freaking
customer. It's a whale. You know, like
if you're a real estate agent and you
sell $500,000 homes and you're working
with a first-time VA home buyer and
they're going to buy one home and then a
whale comes in and they're like, "Hey,
we want to buy 10 $500,000 homes. Who
are you going to answer the phone to
first?" Right? I mean, I actually have
right here a 5090
uh GPU and and these things, honestly,
these are a total beast. I mean, it's
really remarkable because the vast
majority of what you see here is just
cooling. But this very chip I bought
probably for somewhere around $2500 when
it first came out, which was already a
premium. These are currently selling for
about $4,900, which means they've gone
up nearly double in value. We've got,
you know, most of this is obviously
cooling, right? Uh you've got the heat
sinks in here. You've got three fans.
Some of the models for the smaller
chips, they'll sell with two fans. Uh
you got some of the capacitors in the
back right here. Under this is actually
where the die sits and the brain. Uh the
die is really the chip, right? Uh this
is just the printed circuit board, that
PCC right here. And most of this, like
85% of this is frame and cooling. And uh
that actually becomes relatively
important for what we're going to talk
about because a lot of these other
stocks
uh relate to some of the other
components of these GPU chipsets. So uh
Nvidia has obviously confirmed a direct
deal with Elon Musk. Uh and Elon calls
Nvidia's chips just simply the best. at
13,000 racks of GB300 server racks,
you're going to start seeing guidance
increase for Nvidia probably starting in
the fourth quarter of 2026. And this is
something that I consider part of the
second hardware rally post ceasefire.
Let me just be clear about that. In our
course member liveream, we've been
projecting that there will be a second
hardware rally. This is what we were
talking about in July when we're buying
the dip in July because Leo fold is
getting blown up. I'm not trying to
pitch you on this. I'm just trying to
give you just like insight like this is
what we've been talking about. Okay,
some of these things like it's it's
okay. I'm just going to share with you.
Appreciate you being here. The second
hardware rally is mostly in my opinion
driven by Elon spend because it's going
to massively revise up projections that
these companies are giving for actual
growth. And mind you, when we look at
Nvidia, this puppy is sitting at a 75%
gross profit margin. And they bring to
the bottom line out of all of their 81.6
billion of revenue, they bring 71.4%
to their net income. That's insane. Some
of the stocks that we're going to look
at are sitting at like 9% net, 18% net,
20%, 28% net. Those are normal net
income margins. 71.4%. I mean, this is
in in like the memory world for this AI
blow. It these are insane margins. And
of course, the biggest issue for Nvidia
and one of the reasons it's been stuck
at plus or minus $200 is because people
have been worried about growth forecasts
and the potential for those growth
forecasts to turn negative in the
future. But even though there's that
potential for those growth forecasts to
turn negative in the future, the one
thing that could actually turn that
negative to a positive for longer is
Elon. [laughter]
Right now, Nvidia is only up 20% uh year
to date since being the despite being
basically the largest direct beneficiary
of SpaceX. And it has nothing to do with
the monetization of Twitter. It has
nothing to do with the monetization of
uh ads on you know through Grock or Gro
subscription subscriptions and it really
has nothing to do with contract renewal
for SpaceX which is a big debate people
debate like can Anthropic or will
Anthropic or Google actually renew at
these crazy rates or they only doing it
because they're trying to pump their
investments in SpaceX.
Nvidia doesn't give a flying f.
If Nvidia actually ends up the
beneficiary of the all-in like $320
billion version, that's going to lead to
an extra what maybe $100 billion to $150
billion of revenue for Nvidia. That's
about 30% over the 2028 fiscal year
estimates for Nvidia. I mean, think
about it. just just look at it right
now. So right now at $81 billion, uh if
you annualize that out, that's about
$324 billion. So if you add another, you
know, $140ish billion, that's going to
be somewhere close to 30% more in annual
revenue for this company because of one
buyer. And that one buyer is somebody
who is drunk on AI. And maybe he's going
to be right. Maybe he's going to be just
so perfectly brilliant about this and
timed it excellently. He's done
fantastic things in the past. You know,
betting against Elon is, you know, you
have to time it right. [laughter] You
know, you can you can bet against Tesla
at the top. You know, you could somebody
and I feel bad for them, but I saw
actually just somebody I just bookmarked
this. Somebody just put a $3.2 million
$3.3 million short in for SpaceX. uh and
uh they they post the screenshot here,
but what blows my mind is uh they
actually kind of mislead people because
they really only put $1.5 million in.
They just put it in on a 2x leveraged
ETF on the, you know, the short side.
And I'm like, bro, you're going 2x short
when it's literally at its fib bottom.
[laughter]
Like Friday morning, people thought I
was bearish on it. And and again, when
people watch the full videos, I I even
said Thursday morning, I'm like, "Look,
people can't reasonably sell their
lockup shares yet cuz they don't have
them yet. This puppy is going to retrace
and its next test is 133. We said that,
you know, when it was like 114.
Look at it. 13 33 is literally the first
retracement line and that's where we
stopped. I feel bad for the guy shorting
right now, but again, this is not a
SpaceX video. It's supposed to be about
these these stocks."
SpaceX right now is expecting to use the
GB300
in most of these new facilities, but
Macro and and Mini Hard, you know, by
the time they actually start getting
ready to install these GPUs,
Reuben might be available. And if Reuben
is available and we end up getting to a
full 10 gigawwatts that Elon ends up
spending, which would require raising a
lot of capital, more on that in just a
moment, well then Nvidia's revenue could
actually explode to, you know, well,
well, the total spend basically could
explode from those estimates that we saw
of two, you know, 320 to $275 billion
that could explode to like 400 to 480.
It gets ridiculous. And then Nvidia's
portion of that would be even greater.
So their 2028 estimates solely because
of Elon Macro hard, MiniHard, Terraab,
original Colossus expansions
solely because of Elon, we could
literally jack up the estimates for
Nvidia. You could potentially be having
to increase their estimates to the tune
of 50%. So the estimates might
ironically be low for the coming years.
And really the person you have to look
to for the capex cycle is Elon. The I
mean if the guy's essentially we'll
still for the purposes of this video
still call him a trillionaire even
though that he's sort of like on the
margin of that. Oh my gosh you're a
marginal trillionaire. You're only a 900
billionaire [laughter] you know
whatever. Like if that's what he wants
to blow his money on fine.
Now, what's interesting about this is
plus Reuben, which is much more
expensive per rack. You know, a rack
probably is around $4 million. You need
Envy Link, which is another 500k to
million per rack. And Infiniband, you
need Nvidia paid out on shipment. Yeah,
there's a risk that Google ends up
cancing if uh Elon can't deliver on
time, but honestly, I think that's
unlikely because Google's locked up. And
if Google cancelled and SpaceX would
tank and they would just shoot
themselves in the foot and they'd have
to report bad earnings. There's no way
Google's cancelling. They're tied to the
balls of Elon. [laughter]
Then on top of this, you have the Vera
Rubin CPU coming, which I think a lot
like the market honestly I think has
forgotten uh that
there is a CPU coming from Nvidia. Now,
I know a lot of Nvidia bulls are like,
"I know, Kevin. That's just like, don't
tell them. I want to keep buying it
cheap." But, um, it's actually a
fantastic thing. I have, uh, an AMD CPU
that's, uh, probably I mean, the one of
the computers that I have is probably
somewhere around a 10 grand computer. I
mean, it's just the best AMD CPU, the
best power supply, the 5090s in there.
We got some CPU. We got actually, we
just ordered another six90s. Um that's
for for what we're doing with reinvest
but um but yeah I mean like AMD is a
good CPU but Vera CPUs are ARMbased
server CPUs and while some analysts are
including them in their price targets I
don't think people realize that if Elon
buys every one of those Vera CPUs the
pricing power is going to be massive on
the CPU side alone and this is where
things get really interesting because we
could actually look at the valuation for
NVIDIA. So, if we go to uh the
app.mmeke.com
web page, which uh uh you know, course
members have access to all of this and
uh and then of course you can download
this. You could use the app on your
phone too. Meet Kevin app on Android or
Google. But if we go to the
app.mmekevin.com website, the web portal
for this, uh we've got some notes from
me obviously, but we we'll skip some of
that since we're talking about it. Um
the moving average on pricing power did
have a little dippy-dood law. Some of
these dips on pricing power are expected
to be temporary. Uh and and really their
margins are right back to 75% in the
last earnings. We're actually going to
update this software to where we use a
little bit more of an exponential moving
average which will give more weight to
what pricing power has done recently and
it'll actually pump up the pricing power
valuation uh of of u our algo for this.
Uh but what's really interesting is this
particular stock uh I think has a new
valuation target based on uh you know
probably a mid2s to higher twos peg
ratio uh that that moves this stock to
$795 to $850.
That's roughly where we price this thing
as a fair value. Now momentum can drive
this higher or lower like leopold could
drive this lower. Momentum could drive
this higher but the company right now is
trading for a 25p ratio. Its forward
growth projections are 34%.
Per year for the next four years which
means it's trading for less than a one
peg right now which is crazy. The
current peg I have right here is.76.
That's really low and that's a price to
earnings growth ratio. we use that over
just PE ratios. If you just use PE
ratios, I think you're unfairly looking
at the stocks because you're not
factoring in the growth. Uh but you
know, one of the reasons why memory
stocks look low on growth. And this is
really a topic for a different video,
but it applies to Nvidia too is people
believe that the growth will be cyclical
and therefore the growth rates won't
last. And so that's where somebody like
Elon can obviously help that spend go.
Uh but you know it's it's not just Elon
like we have some AI uh sort of uh or I
should say some uh insights on the AI
right here. The Blackwell inference ramp
acceleration the NVL link 72 uh
deployment or yeah deployments are
scaling across hyperscalers. Uh this
accelerates token generation economics
directly compressing inference costs by
60% versus prior generations. there's
going to be even more compression in
token and costs uh for the Vera Rubin uh
you know level products when they come
out. It's going to be really incredible.
Uh in addition to that uh the CPU TAM
expansion here which I think is
critical. The new ARMbased Vera Rubin
CPUs co-designed with Reuben GPUs target
Agentic AI orchestration. This alone
creates a $20 billion revenue
opportunity per year. Not huge right
now, right? Because if you look at that
$20 billion out of their annual of like
324, it's you know what, maybe 7 8% or
whatever. But I actually think Elon
could drive so much demand for these
that the prices go up and you actually
get higher margin CPU, right? And then
of course network revenue that is
critical. That's going to be important
for our next stock as well. And there's
more that you could see in here as well,
which I think is really exciting. Uh red
flags uh would be things like uh you
know delays for the H200 to China. Less
worried about this. I think the market
has really unpriced a lot of this with
China. We we don't even get a lot of
volatility anymore when there's China
news on this particular company.
Obviously a heavy reliance on vendor
financing the circular financing. The
hyperscalers represent 50% of data
center revenue exposing Nvidia to a
potential capex deceleration. Of course,
like we already know that the whole
argument here is that Elon is like he's
going to spend. And the thing about Elon
is as long as the stock performs okay,
like it stabilizes somewhere, which it
probably willish around here, um, he's
going to be able to call up banks and
just borrow more and more money and he's
going to blow every single dollar of
that on
hardware. Now, the next one, Marll.
Okay, so Marll is fascinating because
they create custom silicone for
companies like AWS and Microsoft. They
call them XPUs, basically AS6, uh, and
and products that, you know, other
competitors to Nvidia could use in their
server racks or their data centers. The
problem is you don't want to buy Marll
XPUs and then get excluded from using
Nvidia products, right? Well, don't
worry. There's a solution. Smart good
old Jensen has said, "No, no, no, no. If
you need to use Obviously, we prefer you
buy Nvidia." He's literally said this on
stage. It's great. Obviously, we'd
rather you buy Nvidia, but if you do buy
the XPUs from Marll, we have this new
architecture called Envy Link Fusion.
And it's a fancy way of saying keep
using your A6, your XPUs, whatever you
want. If you want to adopt the NV link
fusion architecture, we can enable you
to integrate with our Nvidia hardware
like our GPUs or our Vera CPUs or
whatever. This now lets basically Nvidia
absorb these other chips of the data
center and Nvidia to just take control
of everything. Now, Google TPUs have not
yet joined the Envy Fusion partnership.
Marll is one of the first adopters, but
a lot of people actually see that as a
structural advantage for Marll because
while Nvidia wants to do this in the
data center. Come here, baby. Come here.
Come here. Come here. Come here. Right.
Uh Marll is like, "Hey, I got these
chips over here. I want you to hug me,
daddy. How do I get in?" Uh here we'll
make this little product for you and
it'll let my arm do this [laughter]
right now. This is interesting for
SpaceX because the Terrafab D3 chips and
the AI6 chips, D3 for orbital, AI6 chips
for like FSD and Optimus robots, AI5 and
AI6 chips, they're going to need Envy
Link Fusion to run alongside of all this
Nvidia stuff good old Elon is blowing
money on. So
NVLink Fusion gets more wellknown, more
popular, and indirectly suggests that
ASIC manufacturers like Marll can
continue to sell their custom silicone
to anyone without somebody being worried
that they're not going to be able to be
incorporated into like the Terafab or
whatever. So technically, you could see
Marll chips inside of the Terraab. Now,
those are likely to be custom Tesla
products, especially since they want to
fabricate themselves or Starlink or
SpaceX products. Again, they want to
manufacture the stuff themselves. That's
fine. Sort of be like, you know, a
parallel competitor to Marll, but that's
okay. The whole idea is the more popular
Envy Link Fusion becomes, the more
customers are comfortable buying
products like the Marll custom chips.
Great. So you've got like not a direct
beneficiary here. It's more of a, oh,
okay, this makes Envy Link Fusion likely
more popular and people's radar. Hey, we
need chips today. Hey, let's go buy some
more Marll chips. Obviously, then there
are other uh long shots for Marll as
well. uh CPOS, you've got uh the future
base station uh AI ideas which is sort
of the AI ran that Jensen and Marll CEO
talk about. This is really the idea that
in the future, you know, your cell phone
like a, you know, a Google phone or your
iPhone or your iPad or whatever will be
able to run a lot of inference directly,
but you'll need access to underlying
data. And the way you could get that is
potentially from base stations where
T-Mobile has its antennas or whatever,
right? and Marll and uh Nvidia have
partnerships
to produce the chipsets that would
enable exactly that. So rather than only
the data centers having the data, some
of that data center workload also sits
at base stations or these sort of nodes
for 5G and 6G technology. That's more
the future call option. Near-term, it's
like, okay, this popularizes NVLink.
Probably good for Marll. Where's their
valuation sitting? Valuation, we got
them at about a $370
uh fair value represents about a 69%
upside from here. Forward growth sits at
about 35%. $4 of EPS for Jan 27. Average
growth of 35% is out four years. Uh
right now, they're sitting at about a 15
peg, I want to see. Let's see here.
We'll find it. We got the moving
average, the insights,
uh 143 is the current PEG ratio for
this. Uh and uh fundamentals, you know,
put this around that 350 377ish range.
Momentum could drive this higher or
lower. Margins have been expanding,
which is nice. I like seeing that on the
chart. Uh we've got, if we jump down
over here into insights, we could see
there it is. One of the first things you
see is the strategic partnership with
Nvidia to integrate custom silicone and
optical networking directly into the
NVIDIA ecosystem. Jensen still really
likes copper as much as possible. Uh
Marll thinks we're going to transition
to fiber optics even inside of the racks
and the data centers themselves which
are mostly copper right now.
If we get to the point where like a
Broadcom isn't pushing just copper, uh
although they do have some optical
options as well, and we really
transition to optics, huge upside
opportunity for Marll. So, it's not
clear if
Terrafab will be an Ethernet-based data
center or an optics-based data center.
If you figure that out and you figure
out it's one or the other, that's either
bearish or bullish for Marll. It's
probably more like base case and bullish
for Marll. It's something to pay
attention to in Elon's commentary,
right? Uh interconnect growth
acceleration. Great. We've got uh
forecast up their optics revenue, custom
silicon designs, $10 billion targets. Uh
data center interconnect business, great
switch. And we could read you could
pause the screen here and read some of
this. Uh there's a lot of very exciting
information about what uh this company
is doing. Uh so but that's just a little
overview. Okay, great. Now let's get on
to the next company. So the next one is
a much smaller company. Uh this one I
mean you have to look Marll is sitting
at right now $191 billion market cap.
Nvidia sitting at a $5.4 trillion market
cap. This next one we're going to talk
about is Teeny, which does increase
potential volatility. Well, relatively
teeny. It's still a decently sized
company. Uh, this company is called
Lattis Semiconductor, LSCC.
This is a field programmable Gatorade,
uh, you know, company. So, they
manufacture these. Uh each server rack
historically has had one to two of these
and we're expecting these to go to maybe
three to four per server rack. Now keep
in mind these are relatively cheap
products. So it it's not like you're
getting massive revenue from here.
Although server revenue does represent
about 38% of Lattis's revenue and that's
expected to grow. But because they're
cheap, their upside is lower. Uh but
because it's a small company, it could
have more volatility to the upside,
especially as we see more FPGAAS inside
of actual rocks. They also bought a for
firmware and platform management play
that should increase their margins even
more. But keep in mind, every single
GB300 and Vera Rubin has embedded F uh
GPA. And so let's look at a potential
price target for these. So their margins
unfortunately as they've been trying to
integrate the firmware company that they
bought and recently have been falling a
little bit. Management does expect that
those are going to increase. Their
current PEG ratio sits at just 0.42
which is on the low side. Uh that is
based on the growth that we have been
seeing and that's some analysts expect
going forward which is essentially a
doubling of earnings per share. If we
see slower growth and we see closer to
40 or 50% growth which some other
analysts expect then the future stock
price for this might be lower. So right
now it trades at a 61% or 61 PE ratio.
If you expect 100% growth that's how you
get less than a one peg. But if you're
expecting 40% growth then you're at
about a 1.5 peg. Now, the average
estimates we have over the next 2 years
are very volatile. There is no good
4-year estimate for the company. It's
too small. So, I think on the high side,
the upside valuation could be $763
bucks. On the lower side, it could be
around $225,
which obviously gives it uh less
potential growth. If we jump into here,
LL uh LSCC, you can see it's about 130
bucks. uh it's come down during the Leo
fold era over here and again it's about
an $18 billion market cap. So uh that
small component manufacturer uh inside
of Iraq uh I think these things are like
a few bucks a piece honestly. Uh let's
find out how much is an LSCC field
programmable gate array product inside a
server rack like GB300. Let's find out.
Let's just see what it says. So, a few
bucks. Uh, yeah. Okay. So, an individual
chip inside of a server rack uh from um
from Lattis typically cost $15 to $50.
So, so these are cheap. And again, the
idea is, hey, can they latch on and get
multiple of these inside of each
motherboard? Right. Look at this. A
single completed server rack can contain
$1,500 to $5,000 worth of Lattis
hardware and integrated firmware.
Kind of interesting, right? Smaller,
more speculative. So, obviously more
risk. Now, let's get into the next one,
which is actually cooling chips. Now, uh
on my AMD CPU on, you know, sort of my
main larger computer, I water cool it.
This puppy is fan cooled right here and
it's got these three massive fans and it
needs a lot of cooling. That little die
gets really really hot especially if
you're running 4K products on it. So
only imagine data centers how much
cooling they need. And this is obviously
where Vertive comes into play. every
GB300 rack at 125 kilowatts of power,
which you know, one of those racks is
like two and a half times our average
household, you know, hourly power usage.
So, that's crazy. And then they've got
thousands of these racks, right? But
anyway, they require liquid cooling and
chillers. Nvidia is going to get paid
regardless of whether or not the SpaceX
contracts renew. But guess who else is
also going to get paid? Vertive and uh
LSCC right so that's a good thing for
these puppies now when we actually think
about this we kind of for vertive think
okay what are the margins for this
company and how much pricing power do
they really have
a decent amount of pricing power if you
jump over here to their margins uh we
can see that their operating margins
have been growing close to 20% on
operating margins
and gross margins are sitting around
37%. For a manufacturer at 18.8% and
growing, this is actually pretty decent.
The company's got a forward uh earnings
per share estimate of $6.68.
Forward growth expectations over the
next four years about 23% per year. Uh
maybe if you just use the next three
years, you get to about 28% average
growth. That's because there's actually
a negative at the end. But because Elon
is drunk selling or drunk drunk buying
here, selling, you know, his his maybe
financing, right, or shares available,
the sucketing, but it but really buying
this hardware, uh we could potentially
see their margins move up and we could
see a higher average growth rate. So, if
we assume about a 28% average growth
rate over the next 3 years, this
particular stock could end up getting to
a pretty wide range here. And it really
just depends. It's a smaller company, so
it just depends on that growth rate.
We're going to go 23, we're going to go
28. The uh growth rate we're going to be
using here is going to be 28.2%. At
28.2%
with those climbing margins, we're
looking at a fair value potentially of
$390.
Uh, so I think between 270 to 390 is
probably a range for Vertive. Uh, if I
pull Vertive right now, you could see
it's actually sitting already at that
270 range. So, the upside's a little bit
more restrained on the more conservative
end of that estimate. Definitely still a
potential though on the more bullcase
scenario. This one also more volatile
though, just because we don't have as
many estimates for this one going
forward. Uh, smaller companies. is I
mean this is a it's a hundred billion
dollar market cap so it's not that small
but some of the companies just don't get
as much analyst love as some of the
giant companies uh let's go take a look
at some of the notes for Vertive here so
what I find interesting here is that
operating margins are rising we've seen
this on the chart that is good and that
has been accelerating in the quarter
this is what changed this quarter this
is on the uh again the meet Kevin appre
and system convergent management
highlights The strategic pivot towards
converged pre-fabricated solutions which
bundle power thermal and IT uh IT
infrastructure increases per site
content capture shortens development
cycles and creates higher switching
costs basically structurally sucking
more people into that uh you know
vertive ecosystem. Nvidia is already
kneedeep in them. So this is really like
I like to call it an Nvidia proxy.
Management confirmed that incremental
service margins service margins aligned
with the 30 to 35% range. It's a smaller
portion of their income but service is
something to pay attention to as well as
the 800vt DC architecture. This is
something that Jensen has talked about.
Uh I think the I think this might be
Vera Rubin Vera Rubin. Uh let me see
here. DC Vera Rubin architecture uh will
include 800 uh volt uh DC power
architecture. That's what I thought. And
remember I said earlier in the video
that I think Elon is going to end up
moving to Vera Rubin as soon as they
come out. The way to look at that is the
GB300
essentially doesn't require the 800vt DC
architecture but you can use it. So if
somebody builds it builds a data center
with 800 volt DC, you could still use
the GB300 and you need it for the next
in infrastructure set the um Vera Rubin
sets. Anyway, I think this is really uh
useful to know that uh Vertive is uh is
is part of this stack as well across the
entire IT stack for broader liquid
cooling deployments, not just chip level
cooling.
The actual data centers themselves got
hot too. [laughter] You ever been in a
room with a lot of these puppies
running? It It gets toasty.
But anyway, uh I love this line. The
order backlog is Elongating
[laughter]
to 12 to 18 months delivery windows.
This is going to be another thing where,
you know, I think Elon goes in and says,
"Look, man, I'll pay more. Get me ahead
of the line." He doesn't care, man, if
the company loses money. It's like in
the Economist interview where they're
like, "Hey, but you know, when are you
guys going to make money?" He just sort
of beats around the bush and laughs it
off. Like he's trying to get to Mars,
man. He doesn't care about EPS next
quarter. [laughter]
Whatever, man. These companies do. So,
um, uh, let's see here. Bring your own
power and micro grid integration. The
rise of behind the meter energy
solutions is driving demand for
Verivives's integrated powertrain and
bees control technology. By positioning
itself as a system level orchestrator
for micro grids and direct current
architecture, Vertive is capturing
adjacent revenue streams that complement
traditional data center infrastructure
deployments. Yeah. So basically there's
a lot of talk that uh these future data
center expansions are trying to do
everything in their power. pun intended
to not rely on the grid. It is
politically unpopular. It is uh time
delay unpopular mostly because the grid
say, "Hey, we can't support you. You're
just going to have to wait." And the
data center sucks, you know. So, a lot
of these data center companies are or
builders are incorporating not just um
Bloom Energy style fuel cells, but also
solar, wind, whatever they can. Nuclear.
probably still too early for obviously,
right? Uh and of course gas turbines are
are are the big uh fun one right now,
which uh this company Boom I know is um
trying to take their supersonic jet
engine designs and and sell them as gas
turbines, which I always think is very
interesting. Uh but but yeah, I mean
this is this is a very interesting one.
This company has a forward uh guidance
for growth of only about 15.7%.
Honestly, might be pretty low. net
margins around 17% and uh they expect to
make $1346 per share at the end of 2026.
That puts us, you know, slightly bel
slightly below a one peg, honestly. So,
so there's definitely some upside on
this stock from the valuation. We've
also got margin expansion, which is
fantastic. Increases their cash flow as
well. We've got um uh you know, an
expansion of where they're putting their
products. Of course, there are some
risks on relying on supper suppliers.
Those are some of the risks. I've
already read through all of this. So,
anyway, that's how we get to about that
$390 price target. Obviously, potential
upshots there on pricing power with
Elon. Uh, and that's what you're really
going to need to kind of keep seeing
that push here on Vertive. The next one
is called Eaton. Eaton is an interesting
one because even though they are also a
well electrical supply manufacturer and
a water cooling provider, data center
orders are up 85% year-over-year.
They're quote unquote leading the 800vt
DC transition and their margin is
expanding expanding. You've got liquid
cooling integration and synergies blah
blah blah blah blah. Great. A lot of
good things. There is a red flag that's
listed over here. First of all, we got
four days to cover uh elevated short
squeeze risk. Fine. But I want you to
see this. The balance sheet strength is
absolute trash.
Why is it 006? Let me show you. I'm
going to use the annual report. This is
using the last quarterly. So, I'm
actually using the older report right
here. But I just want you to see it on
an annual basis what's going on over
here. So, uh first of all, look at their
current debt. their current debt. None
of this is deferred, mind you. This is
literally current portion of long-term
debt, accounts payable, other current
liabilities, acred compensation. All of
this is straight up debt. $9.3 billion.
That's grown in the last quarter. So,
you can see that delta, right? It's
getting worse. On top of that, look at
that. Long-term debt, pension
liabilities, postretirement benefits.
Here we have our first deferred income
taxes, but it's a drop in the bucket
compared to other current liabilities.
Dude, I've got uh you know what? 9 to 11
billion of current debt plus another 12
long. And if I come up here to cash,
bro, where's the cash? I got like 700
maybe $800 million of cash. The cash is
exploded. Like there's no cash. It's
gone. When I say exploded, as in that
typically means go up. No, in this case,
it's just gone. right now. They have
accounts receivable and they have
inventory, but man, they are running a
tight ship. So, if I actually go over
here to financing,
uh, they still have to pay dividends.
For some reason, they're repurchasing
shares at all-time highs. That blows my
mind as well. And so, of course, they're
having to borrow more than they're
refinancing because they're limited on
cash. So, some issues here with Eaton,
uh, that even though they could do well
on these orders from SpaceX, we'll see.
There are some red flags here. You've
got $1346
of earnings per share. So, if I divide
into that 448 price we've got right now,
I'm looking at a 33 PE ratio on forward
growth of 1573 puts me at about a 2.1
peg already with 17% margins. Dude, the
there's not much room left in this
puppy. Uh, and so sometimes I, you know,
I don't only want to mention companies
that that's like, oh yeah, this is
really exciting. It's like, I can be
excited about this, but but much less
excited than others. You know, I mean,
the upside is way lower. Uh, you know,
maybe their growth will really impress
to the upside. But, you know, as you can
see, we've got red flag on balance sheet
and on the moving average, which is
pretty clear. Uh so you know from when
when you look at the chart itself and
its margins are you know while we had
that talk about a 90 you know 90 basis
point move in the quarter we're still
kind of seeing this curvature over here
that's not as ideal uh for this
particular play. Next one is Schneider
Electric. This is a French company. A
lot of people are excited about them for
data centers but data centers only make
up about 20% of their revenue. It is an
ADR an OTC stock. ADR, American
Depository Receipts, French company
again. So it gets a little bit more
complicated to value because they
forecast $11.76
of earnings per share, but you have to
actually divide that by five to get the
earnings per share for an ADR. So that's
$2.35.
All right. So 70 divided by call it
$2.35
divided by 235. That puts me about 30
times PE with maybe growth of about
1463. I'm already at about a two peg for
this puppy. They've only got net margins
around 13 to 14%. And so the fair price
for this one, I hate to say it, is
actually probably upside down at just
$58.
So not as excited about this from a
momentum point of view, not as excited
from a valuation point of view. So I'm
not going to spend too much time on this
one. Instead, we're going to go to Dell
Technologies.
Now, Dell Technologies is an interesting
one because there's a massive potential
risk that Wells Fargo just reported
where they saw SpaceX send their order
to Foxcon for the GB300 servers. They
might literally be skipping Dell and
going direct. Nope, not guaranteed, but
that's a big issue because the reason
Dell has been skyrocketing so much is
because of this backlog for frankly AI
server margins. AI server margins are
still expected to be mid-s single
digits. They don't clearly disclose the
AI server margins because honestly
they're they're not that great, but they
do a lot of value on these. And so
people really get excited about Dell
stock and and I get it. It's a low
margin business, but it's a high volume
business. This company uh is kind of
also at a relative high. If you look at
Dell over here, we're at Yeah, relative
high. It's at a high [laughter]
$453.
Holy smokes. $453.
If I divide that by their forward
forecast EPS, I got a PEG ratio of 24.5.
And we're looking at growth of maybe
1944 on average over the next four years
puts you at about a 1.26 PEG, but
they're at like 8% margins. So, it's
hard to justify much more than the PEG
ratio where they currently sit. Now, I
want to just be fair and disclose this
because this is a beta product. We're
still working on perfecting this. This
is incorrect because the fundamental
estimate inside this fair value estimate
for Dell is that they're only going to
grow at 10%. That is getting revised up
to about 19%.
So, the realistic forward value is
closer to where they sit now. So, again,
less lower on the fundamental upside. I
do just want to report that this is an
error on our platform. Uh and so I want
to make that clear. Okay. Hopefully
that's helpful. All right. Now, before
we get to the next stock, we got to take
a quick break and talk about how much we
love something called free cash flow
yield. The software companies are really
good at free cash flow yield. Like a
Service Now or Salesforce. Salesforce
sits at like a 13% free cash flow yield.
so good and so freaking juicy right now.
But there is actually a hardware company
that has almost as much free cash flow
yield as some of these software
companies. It is insane and it is
actually the next company on our list.
Take a look at this. This is a chart of
free cash flow yield. That's basically
just how much free cash flow you make
divided by your market cap. So if your
market cap's hundred billion and you
make $5 billion of cash flow, that's a
5% yield, right? Simple math. Look at
this.
Nvidia sits close to 2%. Marll sits like
Palanteer close to 1%. Eton is a little
over 2%. Dell's a little over 2%.
Vertive's like 2 and 12%. Right. Okay,
cool. Where's Nphase? What? Almost 7%
free cash flow yield. And folks, that is
probably one of the only things to like
about Nphase. Well, maybe not the only
thing, but one of the few. Mostly
because in their last earnings call they
did kind of talk up delaying a little
bit the IQ solid state transformers.
That's probably a data center play for
2028. It's going to take time. They're
literally right now doing requests for
proposals and they're talking about how
they're learning a lot. H so it's going
to take some time unfortunately for for
this to be a real data center mover and
to kind of get priced in by markets. Uh
but hey, maybe it'll get priced in in
2027.
probably unlikely to perform until they
start selling or until interest rates
come down. Both of those don't feel like
a near-term play. So, Nphase, not a
near-term play, but it is cheap. Worth
paying attention to that. Uh, it is a
stock that has a $2 forecast earnings
per share for the end of the year. The
stock right now is only trading for like
40 bucks or something like that. $41 if
we pull it up. Uh and so if we divide
Nphase which has plummeted since uh you
know COVID because of the lack of
interest in solar uh if we look at
NPhase right now at about 42 bucks I'll
take $42 I'll divide it by the $24 of
projected EPS that's 20.5 on a PE ratio
they're expecting growth to be in the
neighborhood of 18.6%.
That puts them at about a 1.1 peg. At
27% net margins, they probably deserve
to be around 70 to $70 as a stock. And
the upside play is really interest rates
coming down, free cash flow in the
meantime, and a data center call option.
That's that's my take on end phase. So
undervalued setup. Obviously, uh you
know, margins are are decent. If I go to
operating margin, uh it's gotten a
little low on the operating margin side.
Their actual operating margins are also
forecast to nearly double. So, this is
expected to accelerate as they finally
bottom out on some of that solar revenue
that's really been plummeting since co.
So, this company has its risks. I think
a fair value for this stock is probably
around 77 bucks plus a call option on
interest rates and a 2028 data center
play. Something to keep in mind on this.
Not a big favorite right now. It's kind
of like the stepchild of the bunch if
you will. [laughter] Nothing against
stepchildren. All right. Next one that
we got to look at and the final one that
we've got to look at is ARM. ARM is
really interesting because not only do
companies like Nvidia pay licenses per
CPU core, not GPUs. They don't pay for
the GPUs, they pay for CPU cores,
which we're seeing more and more cores
of, which leads to more revenue for ARM
on a license basis. You have to know
with ARM, you've got really big
connections to China in terms of how
related party revenue shows up. They're
not actually dual listed. They're just
listed over here. And then you get this
related party income that just gets
stated from the Chinese side, which is a
little weird because it could lead to
these crazy fluctuations in that stated
income from them. Bizarre. Uh you also
have them now getting into hardware
manufacturing, which I think is a really
big cash flow risk for the company. It's
one of the reasons on the cash flow
chart they sit so freaking low. Uh that
said, uh OpenAI and Meta are buying
their custom silicon expected to ramp up
in 2027. their AGI CPU revenue is
expected to come out by fiscal 2031,
but the custom silicon is a pricey play
because of the capex that it's going to
cost to get there. In my opinion, this
company has about $223
of earnings per share projected for
March of 2027. And the stock right now,
yeah, let's pull it up and then we can
do a P ratio here. stock right now sits
at oo $282. $282 divided by $223 of EPS
puts me at $126 times. I do have
forecast growth sitting at 47.4 for this
company over the next four years. But
that still already puts me at a 2.67
peg. It basically puts me where you
already want to be for the valuation for
this company. Plus, you've got capex
risks. So, I like the cash flow yield of
Nphase, but it's it's honestly like
almost a little value play out of all of
these because it's in a declining
industry. It benefits in the future
maybe from data centers as a call option
and it benefits from interest rates
coming down in the future and that makes
it a bit of a value play right now just
generating cash. The big favorites from
Elon Musk's buying spree in my opinion,
hands down, Nvidia, Marll, and Lattis
Semiconductor in declining order. The
others are okay, but you could obviously
see my analysis exactly on those. Uh,
Nvidia is dirt freaking cheap. Out of
all of these, Nvidia is dirt freaking
cheap. None of this obviously in this
video is personalized financial advice,
but Nvidia is dirt freaking cheap.
Anyway, [music]
uh I hope you like this sort of overview
and uh we'll see you in the next video.
Thanks so much for watching and we'll
see you. Goodbye and good luck.
>> Why not advertise these things that you
told us here? I feel like nobody else
knows about this.
>> We'll we'll try a little advertising and
see how it goes. Congratulations, man.
You have done so much. People love you.
People look up to you.
>> Kevin Praath there, financial analyst
and YouTuber. [music] Meet Kevin. Always
great to get your take.